Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
- State and Federal Related Materials, 1916-1931
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Information Service, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Information Service, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Landscape Art, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Library, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Library Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Military Science and Tactics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Plant Breeding, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Gilbert, Arthur W.
  - Plant Breeding, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Plant Pathology, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Gregory, Charles
  - Plant Pathology, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Plant Pathology, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Pomology, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Poultry, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Register, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Rural Economy, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Rural Education, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Griffin, F. L.
  - Rural Education, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Rural Engineering, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - J. G. Shurman (President), 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - J. G. Shurman (President), 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - J. G. Shurman (President), 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - J. G. Shurman (President), 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Secretary (College), 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Secretary (University), 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Hitchcock, H. A.
  - Semi-Centennial Executive Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Soils, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Summer School, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Notebook with New York State Federal Laws Affecting College Ag Life; Needs of State Colleges at Cornell Pamphlet
    Bristol, George P.
  - Treasurer's Office, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - University Christian Association, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Burr, George Lincoln
    Geer, William C.
    Whitehair, C. W.
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Animal Industry Bureau, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Rawl, B. H.
  - Attorney-General (State), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Civil Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller (State), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Travis, Eugene M.
  - Comptroller (State), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller (State), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 10 a-f)
  - Department of Education (Albany), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Department of Education (Albany), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Department of Interior (Albany), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Jarvis, C. P.
  - Food and Markets, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Markets and Rural Organization Office, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Brand, D. J.
  - Plant Industry Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Corbett, I. C.
  - State Agricultural Society, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Sessions, F. W.
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Benson, O. H
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Whitman, Governor Charles S.
  - State Relations Service, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Wilson, Commissioner Charles S.
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Allen, E. W. - Chief, Office of Experiment Stations, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Architect (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Association for Agricultural Legislation, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    Taylor, Henry C.
  - Attorney General (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Civil Service, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Comptroller (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Comptroller (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Comptroller (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Dairy Industry, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Department of Interior (Albany), 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Education Department (Albany), 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Entomology, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Extension, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Extension, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Farm Crops (Vegetable Gardening), 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Farm Crops (Vegetable Gardening), 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Federal Legislation Pending, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Floriculture, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Floriculture, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Floriculture, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Forestry, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Forestry, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - General File - list of names suggested, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - General File - matters disposed of, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Invitations to Meeting on December 5, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Landscape Art, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Landscape Art, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Conference of Visiting Farmers, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Conference of Visiting Farmers, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Conference of Visiting Farmers, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Departmental Requirements - Building Matters - what to do, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Departmental Requirements - Building Matters - what to do, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Departmental Requirements - Building Matters - what to do, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Departmental Requirements - Building Matters - what to do, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Departmental Requirements - Building Matters - what to do, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Plant Industry Service, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Pomology, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Conferences - Persons Invited and Attendance, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Conferences - Persons Invited and Attendance, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Letters to Editors, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Letters to Editors, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Building Matters - Miscellaneous, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Building Matters - Miscellaneous, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Poultry, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Poultry, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Rural Engineering, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Rural Engineering, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Secretary of Agriculture - Washington, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Secretary of Agriculture - Washington, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Soils, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Soils, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - War Activities - State Relations Service, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    General
  - War Activities - State Relations Service, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - War Activities - State Relations Service, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    Benson
  - War Activities - State Relations Service, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    Lloyd
  - War Activities - State Relations Service, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    Smith
  - Report on College of Agriculture, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Status of Agriculture, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Whitman, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Wilson, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Wilson, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Vice-Dean - Vice-Director, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Vice-Dean - Vice-Director, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Committee Reports, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Committee Reports, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Committee Reports - Administrative Matters, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Committee Reports - Administrative Matters, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Committee on Country Life, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - American Country Life Association, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - American Country Life Association, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - American Country Life Association, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - American Country Life Association, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Work and Needs of New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Grange Letters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Grange Letters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Grange Letters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Grange Letters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Grange Letters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Grange Letters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Grange Letters re Agricultural College, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Grange Letters re Agricultural College, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Grange Letters re Agricultural College, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Grange Letters re Agricultural College, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Prof. Savage Building Matters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Prof. Savage Building Matters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Prof. Savage Building Matters, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Architect (State), 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Architect (State), 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Attorney-General (State), 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Comptroller (State), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Hogue, George E., Commissioner of Agriculture, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Governor Nathan L., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Governor Alfred E., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Agriculture (Meredith), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Education Department (State), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Education Department (State), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Department of Farms and Markets (State), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Department of Farms and Markets (State), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Department of Farms and Markets (State), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Federal Board for Vocational Education, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Legislative, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - State Agricultural Society, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - State Relations Service (General), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Lloyd, W. A., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Smith, C. B., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Sibley College, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Allen, E. W. (Chief Office of Experiment Station), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Allen, E. W. (Chief Office of Experiment Station), 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Automobile Data, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Automobile Data, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Automobile Data, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Assorted Charities, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Agricultural Missions, International Association of, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Alder, Simon L., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Barlow, Floyd - Students' Alumni, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Barlow, Floyd - Students' Alumni, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Bills, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Blauvelt, George A., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Extension Service News, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Extension Service News, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Farmers' Joint Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Fellowships, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Fenner, Casper, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Inventory, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Lusk, Clayton R., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Machold, H. Edmund, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Mann, A. R. (Expense Accounts), 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Mann, A. R. (Expense Accounts), 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Mann, A. R. (Expense Accounts), 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Mann, A. R. (Personal), 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Morrisville School of Agriculture, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Pratt, George D., Conservation Commission, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Pratt, George D., Conservation Commission, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Pratt, George D., Conservation Commission, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Printing, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Sage, Henry M., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Statistics, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Telephone Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Telephone Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Telephone Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Telephone Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Witter, Daniel P., 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - White, Horace (Governor), 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Y Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Z Miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Thatcher, R. W.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Architect - State, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Pilcher, L. F.
  - Architect - State, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Architect - State, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Graves, Mark
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Comptroller, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Department of Agriculture - Washington, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Department of Agriculture - Washington, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Department of Agriculture - Washington, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Department of Agriculture - Washington, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Department of Agriculture - Washington, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Department of Agriculture - Washington, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Department of Farm and Markets, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    Atwood, George G.
  - Department of Farm and Markets, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Department of Farm and Markets, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Miller, Governor Nathan L., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Miller, Governor Nathan L., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Wallace, Secretary of Agriculture Henry C., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Wallace, Secretary of Agriculture Henry C., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Allen, E. W., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Allen, E. W., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Budget Committee, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    Hewitt, Charles J
    Demars, Leon P.
  - Education Department, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - States Relations Service, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - States Relations Service, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Smith, C. B., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Architecture (State), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Architecture (State), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Attorney General, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Buildings, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Buildings, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 23)